user,review_title,review,date,translated,entities,sentiment,sentiment magnitude
Clare,Fabulous!,"This is a lovely hotel, very well priced for excellent service (Particularity Sajid in the Ocean restaurant), old school style luxe. Location is a little noisy currently due to construction works nearby, not the hotels fault but something to bear in mind if you wish to spend significant time by the pool.",Date of stay: March 2020,"This is a lovely hotel, very well priced for excellent service (Particularity Sajid in the Ocean restaurant), old school style luxe. Location is a little noisy currently due to construction works nearby, not the hotels fault but something to bear in mind if you wish to spend significant time by the pool.","{'name': ['hotel', 'service', 'luxe', 'old school style', 'restaurant', 'Particularity Sajid', 'Ocean', 'Location', 'construction', 'mind', 'pool', 'fault', 'hotels', 'something'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER']}",0.3,1.1
Gillian V,Birthday Treat,I would like to thank Mr Prasanthan for organising the table for Mrs Shehani Rozairo's Birthday Luncheon and also the complimentary cake provided which was a surprise to her. The ambience is as always fantastic and food excellent and the attention excellent.  Thank you once again and will definitely visit again.,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Derek,3 Nights at the Kingsbury,"The bed was the hugest that I have ever slept in! I enjoyed the breakfasts; the dining area was vast and offered a great variety of food. The staff was very helpful and friendly. One morning a waiter named Joseph made a couple of pots of coffee just for us. Another morning a waitress called Nipuni went and brought egg hoppers to my table for me. I loved the location, and I recommend a walk along the beach day or night, when it is bustling with activity.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Loub,Friendly atmosphere,Enjoyed a great stay at Kingsbury Colombo. Amazing friendly staff. Nalintha and Richard front desk were very welcoming and happy to assist us with any enquiries. Highly recommended. Kings Steak restaurant was a great choice for dinner.,Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
roshneil,Identity crisis,"Nalitha was great at check in. Hotel is quite nice, Hotel is having a bit of an identity crisis, it is a cross between a 5 star hotel and a after 6pm sort of turns into a rave type party with the horrendous loud doof doof  music being played until 11pm, it’s  what I would expect from a back packers hostel. For this reason I would not stay here again",Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
S B,Impressive hotel with outstanding food,"Well appointed comfortable rooms.. though the pool facing room actually faces the Barbour which was not nice. The food in the outlets are outstanding . Crab cakes, the  lobster and prawns superlative. The breakfast has a fabulous range.",Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Junhi,"my stay was comfortable, staff friendly, but apart from managers, they need to train more their staff in English","The hotel is one of the oldest one which has been renovated with a fine taste, quite elegant and it has a heritage flair, which I liked very much. The room is small but well organized, the only thing I did not like was the low ceiling, probably they squeezed the building to have more storeys when they renovated.  And many of staff needed to improve their English, otherwise, my stay was comfortable and food in cafeteria is quite good.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Lpa_66,Awesome,Thank you Kingsbury we came in 2017 and loved it once again you were amazing.  The food and service still fantastic and still the most comfortable bed and pilliows had the best nights sleep.  Will definately be our go to hotel in Colombo,Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Colin W,Excellent Hotel with great customer service,Great location and excellent customer service. Rooms are clean and good bathrooms. Breakfast is great and one of the best spreads of food with many choices. Special mention to Chef Jayasinghe for his attitude and willing to help customer needs. Great customer service all around . Overall excellent stay.,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Tanya B,Ocean Seafood Restaurant,"Great seafood restaurant, best in Colombo! We had a delicious meal and drinks. Mussels, squid and curry were super tasty.  Service and ambience are great!  Sajith and Geethaka provided is with the fantastic service!",Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Michelle M,got excellent services,"We got excellent services from waiters, saijth, Chalitha and Amila. Especially the food are fresh seafood. Highly recommended the lobsters, Red Snappers. Good tea, coffee, desserts. Nice view and good chef.",Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Antonio,Great hotel,An excellent hotel in the center of Colombo in Sri Lanka. The room is very clean. The chief of concierge Priyantha is very helpful and friendly such as all the stuff. The pool and the honey beach club is excellent.,Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Mohan S,Best hotel in Colombo,"I have stayed in about 6 different hotels around Colombo and I can easily say that this hotel is the winner. Both in terms of price and the quality of stay  The restaurants are tastefully done. The bar by the pool is amazing place to end your day. If that is not enough there is another cool bar on the rooftop where the view is amazing.  Breakfast : never seen such a wide spread of different food.  Hospitality : this is the aspect which is the best part. You are pampered.  Only drawback : compared to other hotels, rooms here are a bit smaller. In terms of creature comfort, no complaints",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
TAKZ,Harbour court,Sujith gave us a very friendly service and he was very supportive and cared a lot about us and this is what we as customers expect. So it was a wonderful eve and the food was awesome   Loved it 💪😍😍😍,Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
mwick8532,Dinner,Had dinner with friends.Menues all torn and dirty. Complained to manager He said the day manager was in charge.For a five star hotel that is not acceptable. Food good tasty.Good ambience not noisy.No excuse to have torn dirty menues,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Poornima k,Great service,"Today, Visited as a guest directly to the Main restaurant for early morning Breakfast. Mr. Amila ( Duty manager ) was very accommodating.  What a fabulous personalized service we had.  All hotel staff I encountered were friendly, helpful, well presented and efficient. Very Yummy food with huge spread  😋😋😋😋 Pleasant morning with yummy foods.",Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Stephen,Excellent experience,Staff is excellent. Richard at front desk was a great help. Looking forward to our next stay. Excellent location. Food is unsurpassed in Colombo. Room extremely comfortable. Overall excellent experience.,Date of stay: March 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
S Skanda Kumar,Pleasant Stay with excellent Hospitality !,"No sign of the after effects of the incident of last Easter. Well recovered and restored. Restaurant staff were excellent - especially Jason, the man with a smile. The choice of food has somewhat been reduced since the incident last year. However, I must say that there is absolutely nothing wrong with what is on offer now. Well worth a visit to experience the skyline of Colombo and the Indian ocean.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Jayesh K,Wonderful hotel - excellent location & great staff,"The Kingsbury is located very centrally in Colombo with easy access to entertainment, shopping, and business district , where comfort of the guests is of paramount importance , We had a fantastic time at the hotel. Good well equipped rooms ( we booked an executive room) which came with lot of benefits including Lounge access and private check-in, the size of the room is bit smaller but very well furnished , large TV with HD international channels , the toiletries are of luxurious Bvlgari  The breakfast buffet was among the best I have experienced in any hotel anywhere in the world, huge spread, live stations , attentive staff , my special thanks & gratitude to Chef Jason and Chef Jaywardane who everyday of our stay ensured Jain breakfast for my wife , the Masala Tea was simply",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Boyko Bowv,Front office staff,"The staff at office was exceptional and Isuru,Ajith was really help full. The hotel in general is Great with amazing view. The Pool is great, the bar CaLaVi on the roof is really good. Rooms are clean and comfort. I really recommend that hotel   Thank you!",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Quintus A,The best place ever in sri lanka . Kingsbury ocean view restaurant is the best . Niroshan calistus and his team gave us,Superb & excellent service. Very tasty food and unforgettable staff with excellent service.  Thank you so much all of you guys. We will come back again Niroshan & staff we are really satisfied with everything..will visit the ocean kingsbury soon♥️ .,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
micksuzy,Wow,"The Staff of the Kingsbury are outstanding and a special mention must go to Nalitha on reception. What an outstanding representative for this hotel. He was exceptionally polite and helped us with all our requests.  The hotel is absolutely lovely and a must stay if you are in Colombo. We love it, the room is beautiful and clean with a very comfortable bed.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Senash Ariyaratne,Writing a review on the excellent service provided on one of our special days,The ocean restaurant lead by Niroshan and his team gave us a superb service. I would love thank all of them with all my heart. Excellent job done! Their humble attitude was the talk of the party we had,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Mark B,"Great hotel, best food had in Sri Lanka","Had the most amazing steak at this hotel and the best breakfast in Sri Lanka after staying in 7 different hotels.  Nalitha at the front desk was especially helpful on 3 different occasions - sorted out our booking, room, purchases, extended check-out. Was the best well spoken hotel person and helped make our stay even better.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
WolfAUT,Amazing stay...!!,"Dont wann say much... everything there speaks for itself. it was just amazing!  -ambience, cleanliness and appearence of the hotel itself are outstanding. -food is perfect... we loved the breakfast!!! Jason always took care of us so well!! they even have ""real"" coffee and dont charge extra (like ALL other hotels do)...which shows their ambition -a gym equipped with dumbells, barbells, actual weights... rowers, treads etc... AND jacuzzi/sauna/steam  after our stay, we will definitely use colombo and The Kingsbury as our hub when travelling further east... if i could, i would rate it 11 out of 10",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Gillian R,exceptional Colombo hotel,"Breakfast was exceptional and extraordinary - never seen so much choice - western and sri lankan food - waffle/pancake plus Hopper/omelette stations.  Swimming pool was marvellous - long opening hours, large and generally empty.  Check in and out very efficient.  Staff very helpful and knowledgeable.  The location is very central and facilities are of a very high standard. My room was not large but very well appointed with everything required and most importantly very clean with a super comfortable bed and choice of pillows.  Treated like royalty even though I turned up completely dishevelled after a 10 hour train journey",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Skamath,Need to improve on service..,"Staying here for 3 nights from 22nd Feb, to start with Pros: nice location( now partially compromised due to port city construction) to walk near Galle face green, good quality bed..  Cons:1. booked a superior OCEAN view room, was particularl on this and paid extra online. At reception, checked in at around 4pm, and front desk Mr. Ishaack gave us another non sea facing room, saying it is better category. But when we book and pay for ocean view, we expect that or they should not advertise the same. As many other hotels can offer same. 2. First day at breakfast, we were impressed by spread and some nice masala tea, Second day at breakfast found service poor, menu same, but when asked for masala tea again.. the waiter made us wait for more than 15 to 20 min, and at end we went",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
tuan miskin,Lunch@stakebar,"One a gain here we came to take lunch @ stake bar one of the best fine dining in the town.we had beef steaks it was a best stake I aver  had .the cocktail was superb sensation felver thanks to the service crew Denver,sanuja,fateen,and the manager viran will see you soon again thanks very much. Keep doing the good job.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Kanishka W,Dinner at Harbour Court,Harbour Court arguably has the best buffet spread. Hosted five guests for dinner on 23rd of February and the food was amazing as always. Jason who attended to us at the restaurant was extremely attentive and was very service orientated which made our experience even better.,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Kumar,"Great location, excellent service","Had a wonderful stay in Kingsbury Hotel. Was on a business trip and stayed on the executive floor. Excellent service and hospitality, many thanks to Diego and Viloka for making my stay wonderful and pleasant. Would surely return to this hotel again.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Keerthi W,Need Trained staff,Stayed for 3 nites in Dec.unorganized and untrained front office.First time staying here after complete refurbishment.Overall service standards needs to be improved. Breakfast buffet was good.Room amenities excellent.,Date of stay: December 2019,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Dave L,End of our 4 month travels around Asia,"We have stayed in 5* hotels all over Asia and I can honestly say this one had been the best  We are staying in room 302 which is lovely and the housekeeping is exceptional  The breakfast is the phenomenal what a choice, you couldn’t ask for more. We have eaten in all the restaurants the food, the service, and staff are amazing  We could name the staff, but to be honest all the staff are fantastic and it wouldn’t be fair",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Veronica,Habur court,"Here is my regular place. I usually go with my family and sometimes with friends. Most people around me love this place~ It's a huge dining area which offers an excellent selection. Amazingly, so~ tasty. The hotel has a morden ambience. you can enjoy the food with a beautiful music. Service has been friendly on every visit!! extremely accommodating and attentive. I really appreciate all  staffs. especially Buddika and sujith. Harbor court is highly recommended for the best place in Colombo",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
AIreshaK,Nice but would’ve been better,"It was my Third stay within last 6 months and Happy to see Dheeraka from the Reception and Dilshan from the F&B still remembers me. Dheeraka was a lovely young gentleman in the frontline who tried to assist me at his best, unfortunately the housekeeping team did not amazed me this time as they used to do. Few troubles due to cleanliness in the room, no towels, minibar issues etc. So the first day was literally ruined.   However, we were moved to a better room in the midnight by the manager on duty and he arranged all our needs since then!  I must say, the newly renovated main restaurant looks stunning with a huge spreader breakfast buffet. Complements to the chef and his team!    P.S.  Note to the Management : at some point the team explained that the hotel is running out of the",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
tis_12,A great city hotel with a very good offer.,"The Kingsbury is a great hotel that offers a variety of amenities. The bed was very pleasant, the windows well soundproofed and the room very clean. The very friendly staff especially Mr. Madurunga, Mr. Kasun and Mr. Buddika tried very hard to fulfill our wishes.  The quality of the services and the very good value for money rightly deserve the best rating.  Breakfast is first class both in depth and breadth.  We would be happy to recommend this hotel.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Maryzse Mylvaganam,Dinner At The Harbour Room,"We enjoyed a lovely evening with my Family on Sunday for dinner and enjoyed ourselves very much.  There was an endless amount of various different types of deliciously prepared dishes, it was difficult to eat everything 🤭☺😊 We want to say a BIG THANK YOU TO JASON THE YOUNG STEWARD WHO SERVED US..... HE WAS EXTREMELY HELPFUL AND ATTENTIVE TO ALL OUR NEEDS. THANK YOU FOR A LOVELY EVENING!!!  THANK YOU ALL WHO WORK SO TIRELESSLY TO MAKE IT PLEASURABLE EVENING.   We definitely will be back.  Wishing You God's Blessings! Maryzse Mylvaganam.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
RJ MD,"Great location, great facilities and great service","The Kingsbury has all the features you'd expect of a good 5 star hotel, and the rooftop bar, long pool suitable for serious swimmers as well as splashing around, great local breakfast options at the buffet and a superb Chinese restaurant. It goes without saying that the location is absolutely top notch.   I was particularly impressed by the service; due to unforeseen circumstances my wife and I needed to make a number of changes to our booking, all of which were dealt with seamlessly by the friendly and helpful front desk team. Thanks in particular to guest relations manager Fayaz for making our stay so pleasant.",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
k1k2ching,Dinner @ Kingsbury,"The buffet restaurant was good and a varied selection offered however found that the service of dumplings and the chocolates were controlled. For what?? The price one pays should cover it all, shouldn't it? Service staff should not only recommend the higher priced and imported drinks from the list when asked for their recommendations. A well presented restaurant and nice ambience.",Date of stay: January 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Chenee C,Lunch,Very good service. I love the selection of buffet.  Friendly guest and nice ambiance. Love to go back here. Thank you to jani for accompanying us. The staff are also attentive. The place is huge and spacious. Great hotel.,Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
Ramasubramanian M,best property in Colombo,"room is excellent worth for our money. staff or very good and very friendly, i enjoy in executive lounge Miss. Shivangi and Mr. Mohamed or very friendly in executive lounge. this property worth for your money business trip or family trip thank you guys",Date of stay: February 2020,,"{'name': ['None'], 'type': ['OTHER']}",-0.2,0.2
BhavnaSharma,Memorable stay at the hotel,"We had superb stay at the Kingsbury Hotel. Fayaz, Asst Manager and very courteous staff made our stay memorable. Worth staying at the hotel. Huge spread of breakfast menu, luxurious rooms and superb location.",Date of stay: February 2020,"We had superb stay at the Kingsbury Hotel. Fayaz, Asst Manager and very courteous staff made our stay memorable. Worth staying at the hotel. Huge spread of breakfast menu, luxurious rooms and superb location.","{'name': ['stay', 'Kingsbury Hotel', 'staying', 'staff', 'Asst Manager', 'Fayaz', 'rooms', 'breakfast menu', 'location', 'hotel', 'spread'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT']}",0.8,3.5
anne h,Great experience after backpacking,"Nice facilities. Only complaint would be that the service at the restaurant was a bit too attentive. My conversation with my partner was interrupted by several waiters asking if we wanted coffee or something else. This doesn't sound like much, but the experience was similar to tuktuk drivers offering a tuktuk ride nonstop.",Date of stay: February 2020,"Nice facilities. Only complaint would be that the service at the restaurant was a bit too attentive. My conversation with my partner was interrupted by several waiters asking if we wanted coffee or something else. This doesn't sound like much, but the experience was similar to tuktuk drivers offering a tuktuk ride nonstop.","{'name': ['facilities', 'complaint', 'service', 'restaurant', 'partner', 'waiters', 'bit', 'conversation', 'coffee', 'something', 'experience', 'tuktuk drivers', 'tuktuk ride'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'EVENT']}",0.0,1.9
Explorer305451,"Wonderful sevice by Hiras,","Me and my friend had a dinner at harbour court today. Its emazing, excellent food and very friendly stuff.My favourite buffet in town.wonderful service by Hiras and Kasun.keep up the good work. Hope to visit again soon.",Date of stay: February 2020,"Me and my friend had a dinner at harbour court today. Its emazing, excellent food and very friendly stuff.My favourite buffet in town.wonderful service by Hiras and Kasun.keep up the good work. Hope to visit again soon.","{'name': ['friend', 'dinner', 'harbour court', 'food', 'buffet', 'service', 'emazing', 'work', 'stuff.My', 'Hiras', 'Kasun.'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'EVENT', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.5,1.9
Janaka,Harbour court,"Dinner at harbour court is amazing, the ambience is here is nice ,wide variety of food and dessert is available, food is delicious. Jason one of the staff member was very helpful with a smiling face and friendly.",Date of stay: February 2020,"Dinner at harbour court is amazing, the ambience is here is nice ,wide variety of food and dessert is available, food is delicious. Jason one of the staff member was very helpful with a smiling face and friendly.","{'name': ['Dinner', 'harbour court', 'ambience', 'food', 'variety', 'food', 'dessert', 'face', 'Jason one', 'staff member', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,1.8
Kamal S,Harbour court,We had dinner at harbour court very amazing buffet and service special thanks goes to manager prashanthan and sujith they look after very well we were enjoyed our dinner here will come soon keep it your good work always,Date of stay: February 2020,We had dinner at harbour court very amazing buffet and service special thanks goes to manager prashanthan and sujith they look after very well we were enjoyed our dinner here will come soon keep it your good work always,"{'name': ['dinner', 'dinner', 'thanks', 'buffet', 'harbour court', 'sujith', 'manager prashanthan', 'work'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,0.9
Nadda24,Fabulous service by Magana,Came for drinks with friends and needed to sort out an issue and even though Magana didn't have to she totally stepped out and was fabulous! Thank you so much Megana! We are already regulars here and will continue to patronage Honey beach!,Date of stay: February 2020,Came for drinks with friends and needed to sort out an issue and even though Magana didn't have to she totally stepped out and was fabulous! Thank you so much Megana! We are already regulars here and will continue to patronage Honey beach!,"{'name': ['drinks', 'friends', 'issue', 'regulars', 'Magana', 'beach', 'Honey', 'Megana'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'OTHER']}",0.8,2.6
Nuwan12,Romantic evening at Harbor Court,"Myself and my fiancee made a reservation for dinner on valentine day at Harbor court, we should say we were blown away by the service and food provided on that day. Kudos to Kumindra and team. Nothing was too much trouble for them. They went out of their way to make our day special. Buddhika, maduranga and Nipuni were excellent. Their service was flawless. We would definetly comeback. Thanks for the memorable night Kumindra and team.",Date of stay: February 2020,"Myself and my fiancee made a reservation for dinner on valentine day at Harbor court, we should say we were blown away by the service and food provided on that day. Kudos to Kumindra and team. Nothing was too much trouble for them. They went out of their way to make our day special. Buddhika, maduranga and Nipuni were excellent. Their service was flawless. We would definetly comeback. Thanks for the memorable night Kumindra and team.","{'name': ['team', 'fiancee', 'reservation', 'dinner', 'Nothing', 'court', 'service', 'food', 'Kudos', 'way', 'service', 'comeback', 'Kumindra', 'Thanks', 'Kumindra', 'maduranga', 'Nipuni', 'Buddhika'], 'type': ['ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.8,7.0
Vance,Excellent hotel services and staff,Fatten Farzan was exceptionally knowledgeable regarding local establishments in the area of the Kingsbury hotel. His service was excellent and timely sharing value information regarding cultural sensitivities which provide insight regarding local customs and attitudes.,Date of stay: February 2020,Fatten Farzan was exceptionally knowledgeable regarding local establishments in the area of the Kingsbury hotel. His service was excellent and timely sharing value information regarding cultural sensitivities which provide insight regarding local customs and attitudes.,"{'name': ['Farzan', 'sharing value information', 'establishments', 'sensitivities', 'hotel', 'area', 'Kingsbury', 'customs', 'insight', 'attitudes'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,1.8
Randunu D,Dinner buffet,The best place for dinner buffet in the city with a wide variety of food. The staff is friendly and attentive. Very spacious and cozy atmosphere. Food variety includes all the meat varieties with BBQ as well.,Date of stay: February 2020,The best place for dinner buffet in the city with a wide variety of food. The staff is friendly and attentive. Very spacious and cozy atmosphere. Food variety includes all the meat varieties with BBQ as well.,"{'name': ['place', 'dinner buffet', 'city', 'variety', 'food', 'staff', 'meat varieties', 'BBQ', 'Food variety', 'atmosphere'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,3.7
Lalini D,Stayed for 10 days and was absolutely amazing service,The restaurant staff and the kitchen staff were so friendly and attended to all our needs. The Houskeeping staff were also very friendly and paid attention to detail. Very different to our first experience 8 months ago. Will definitely stay there again,Date of stay: July 2019,The restaurant staff and the kitchen staff were so friendly and attended to all our needs. The Houskeeping staff were also very friendly and paid attention to detail. Very different to our first experience 8 months ago. Will definitely stay there again,"{'name': ['restaurant staff', 'kitchen staff', 'needs', 'detail', 'attention', 'experience', 'Houskeeping', 'staff', '8'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.7,3.0
Shanaka A,Dinner,Great service and excellent choice of food options at the Harbours Court restaurant. The desert menu is something to checkout if you come in to dine here. Special thanks to Jani at the restaurant service team.,Date of stay: February 2020,Great service and excellent choice of food options at the Harbours Court restaurant. The desert menu is something to checkout if you come in to dine here. Special thanks to Jani at the restaurant service team.,"{'name': ['service', 'choice', 'desert menu', 'food options', 'restaurant', 'Harbours Court', 'checkout', 'thanks', 'restaurant service team', 'Jani'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON']}",0.8,2.5
Gisela Steinort,One of the best Hotels in Colomo,"Its the second time I visited the Kingsbury and I had the same wonderful experiences like two years ago. The room was phantastic, the Lobby, the Restaurant etc. But the best where the Staff, they where like Family to me  I have to name my favorite Ladies who where:  Nirisha Sachini Dinushi Sajani Beverly Sathsarani  also from the Lobby Sajaya  Fayas Prashanthan Umapathisivam from the Restaurant  All of them did a phantastic Job I will never forget and I really appreciated it. They made the hotel be like my home.  Thanks to all of them and I hope I can come again.  With best regards  Gisela Steinort",Date of stay: January 2020,"Its the second time I visited the Kingsbury and I had the same wonderful experiences like two years ago. The room was phantastic, the Lobby, the Restaurant etc. But the best where the Staff, they where like Family to me  I have to name my favorite Ladies who where:  Nirisha Sachini Dinushi Sajani Beverly Sathsarani  also from the Lobby Sajaya  Fayas Prashanthan Umapathisivam from the Restaurant  All of them did a phantastic Job I will never forget and I really appreciated it. They made the hotel be like my home.  Thanks to all of them and I hope I can come again.  With best regards  Gisela Steinort","{'name': ['Ladies', 'experiences', 'Kingsbury', 'best', 'room', 'Thanks', 'Lobby', 'Restaurant etc', 'Family', 'Staff', 'hotel', 'home', 'all', 'Restaurant All', 'Nirisha Sachini Dinushi Sajani Beverly Sathsarani', 'Lobby Sajaya Fayas Prashanthan Umapathisivam', 'regards', 'Job', 'Gisela Steinort', 'two'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.5,3.9
kavindu p,B day celebration,"Really awesome service have you guys thank u so much and food service and all things are brilliant  Once agin thx and we love to visit this place gain   Want to personally thx miss madushika , because she gave me awesome support to achieve my plan",Date of stay: February 2020,"Really awesome service have you guys thank u so much and food service and all things are brilliant  Once agin thx and we love to visit this place gain   Want to personally thx miss madushika , because she gave me awesome support to achieve my plan","{'name': ['service', 'place', 'food service', 'thx', 'things', 'plan', 'support', 'madushika', 'miss', 'Want'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,0.9
Ewa K,Beautiful hotel,"Stayed one night only on my way to the airport. Hotel is incredible! Clean hotel, staff very helpful and rooms pretty big and very clean. Bar area with the pool is a friendly place to relax. Food in a restaurant very good.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Stayed one night only on my way to the airport. Hotel is incredible! Clean hotel, staff very helpful and rooms pretty big and very clean. Bar area with the pool is a friendly place to relax. Food in a restaurant very good.","{'name': ['way', 'airport', 'Hotel', 'hotel', 'Bar area', 'rooms', 'staff', 'place', 'Food', 'restaurant', 'pool', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.7,3.8
Joseph,Kingsbury harbour court,Good food good service. Great thanks to thilanka and his colleague to serve us well. Helping us on the food and drinks. Ensuring if the food was good and that we needed help or feedback on the food. It was a total good experience here. Highly recommended.  Ps: it is affordable. 25 sgd (3300sri lanka rupees) per pax.,Date of stay: February 2020,Good food good service. Great thanks to thilanka and his colleague to serve us well. Helping us on the food and drinks. Ensuring if the food was good and that we needed help or feedback on the food. It was a total good experience here. Highly recommended.  Ps: it is affordable. 25 sgd (3300sri lanka rupees) per pax.,"{'name': ['thilanka', 'food', 'service', 'thanks', 'experience', 'food', 'colleague', 'food', 'food', 'drinks', 'feedback', 'help', '25 sgd', '3300sri lanka rupees', '25', '3300'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PRICE', 'PRICE', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.6,5.7
Tania,Note of Appreciation for Function held on Saturday 8th Feb. 2020,"Note of Appreciation  We wish to convey our heartfelt gratitude to your wonderful team who assisted us to make our daughter’s birthday a memorable one. The function was on the Saturday 08th February 2020 at the Winchester Hall.   Mr. Upul Senarathna of banquets handled the booking at first and was patient with several emails which was sent by us re function. We were very keen to experience the great service as in the past (function held at the same venue on 23rd January 2016).   Mr. Leshan Dias who took over the duties from Mr. Senarathna, was extremely confident that he will be able to give us the service and standard we desired from a five star hotel. This was an immense consolation to us as it is very seldom that consistency is maintained in today’s hospitality industry.   As",Date of stay: February 2020,"Note of Appreciation  We wish to convey our heartfelt gratitude to your wonderful team who assisted us to make our daughter’s birthday a memorable one. The function was on the Saturday 08th February 2020 at the Winchester Hall.   Mr. Upul Senarathna of banquets handled the booking at first and was patient with several emails which was sent by us re function. We were very keen to experience the great service as in the past (function held at the same venue on 23rd January 2016).   Mr. Leshan Dias who took over the duties from Mr. Senarathna, was extremely confident that he will be able to give us the service and standard we desired from a five star hotel. This was an immense consolation to us as it is very seldom that consistency is maintained in today’s hospitality industry.   As","{'name': ['team', 'Leshan Dias', 'gratitude', 'Appreciation', 'Note', 'service', 'emails', 'daughter', 'Upul Senarathna', 'function', 'function', 'function', 'patient', 'banquets', 'booking', 'venue', 'consolation', 'hotel', 'standard', 'Winchester Hall', 'consistency', 'hospitality industry', 'Mr.', 'duties', 'Saturday 08th February 2020', '23rd January 2016', '23', '2016', 'one', 'five', '2020', '08'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.4,3.3
acanthal,Excellent Hospitality and Service!,"My partner and I stayed at the Kingsbury in December 2019 and was completely blown away by the outstanding warmth and hospitality of all the hotel staff. It’s a beautiful hotel with great restaurants and wonderful facilities. But it’s the staff that really makes this place so welcoming. All the staff and managers we encountered were lovely but special mentions go to our awesome room cleaner Priantha Rajanayake, Eranga Silva from Churros and Jani Vinoth Benadict and Jason from the Harbour Court Restaurant for looking after us so well. Highly recommend.",Date of stay: December 2019,"My partner and I stayed at the Kingsbury in December 2019 and was completely blown away by the outstanding warmth and hospitality of all the hotel staff. It’s a beautiful hotel with great restaurants and wonderful facilities. But it’s the staff that really makes this place so welcoming. All the staff and managers we encountered were lovely but special mentions go to our awesome room cleaner Priantha Rajanayake, Eranga Silva from Churros and Jani Vinoth Benadict and Jason from the Harbour Court Restaurant for looking after us so well. Highly recommend.","{'name': ['partner', 'Kingsbury', 'staff', 'hotel', 'warmth', 'hospitality', 'hotel staff', 'restaurants', 'facilities', 'place', 'managers', 'Priantha Rajanayake', 'staff', 'Jason', 'Eranga Silva', 'Churros', 'Jani Vinoth Benadict', 'Harbour Court Restaurant', 'mentions', 'December 2019', '2019'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'DATE', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,4.1
Eighty Flavours,Classy stay in Colombo,Classy comfortable historic hotel in the perfect location in Colombo - right in between Galle Face Green and the main train station. Also next door to the Ministry of Crab. Nice pool and great buffet breakfast with made to order hoppers! Be sure to check out the rooftop bar for sunset drinks. Small but well equipped gym. Great service.,Date of stay: January 2020,Classy comfortable historic hotel in the perfect location in Colombo - right in between Galle Face Green and the main train station. Also next door to the Ministry of Crab. Nice pool and great buffet breakfast with made to order hoppers! Be sure to check out the rooftop bar for sunset drinks. Small but well equipped gym. Great service.,"{'name': ['hotel', 'location', 'train station', 'Colombo', 'Galle Face Green', 'door', 'pool', 'buffet breakfast', 'sunset drinks', 'Ministry of Crab', 'rooftop bar', 'gym', 'service', 'hoppers'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.7,4.4
Lloydperera,Horrible Customer Service is an understatement.,"Kingsbury has everything to offer, but their horrible customer service needs to be looked into. Poor management is the problem. Employee name - Ajith, and the Duty  Manager (Didn't get his name). I'm sure they hired these individuals right off the street to keep operating cost down. We usually visit the Honeybeach pub once a week to catch up. After a chilled out evening, my friend proceeded to collect his vehicle from their glorious carpark. Lol. We were confronted by a midget named ""Ajith"". He had very ""Suge Knight"" attitude. He requested a ""bill"" from the pub. Apparently, if you need to collect your vehicle from their carpark, you need show your expenditure at this establishment. So ""No bill, No Vehicle"". We took our concerns to the ""Duty Manager"". His response was priceless.",Date of stay: February 2020,"Kingsbury has everything to offer, but their horrible customer service needs to be looked into. Poor management is the problem. Employee name - Ajith, and the Duty  Manager (Didn't get his name). I'm sure they hired these individuals right off the street to keep operating cost down. We usually visit the Honeybeach pub once a week to catch up. After a chilled out evening, my friend proceeded to collect his vehicle from their glorious carpark. Lol. We were confronted by a midget named ""Ajith"". He had very ""Suge Knight"" attitude. He requested a ""bill"" from the pub. Apparently, if you need to collect your vehicle from their carpark, you need show your expenditure at this establishment. So ""No bill, No Vehicle"". We took our concerns to the ""Duty Manager"". His response was priceless.","{'name': ['Ajith', 'management', 'everything', 'customer service', 'Kingsbury', 'friend', 'name', 'Duty Manager', 'Employee name', 'Duty Manager', 'pub', 'vehicle', 'carpark', 'individuals', 'street', 'midget', 'vehicle', 'carpark', 'bill', 'establishment', 'Vehicle', 'Honeybeach', 'response', 'concerns', 'expenditure', 'pub', 'cost', 'attitude', 'Suge Knight', 'bill'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'EVENT', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART']}",-0.3,6.7
Susmitha S,Buffet,"The place is nice to hangout, the people are so friendly and love to visit over again and again.  Specially, the food is tasty with variety of menus and a ambience is so perfect for a family to relax and enjoy.",Date of stay: February 2020,"The place is nice to hangout, the people are so friendly and love to visit over again and again.  Specially, the food is tasty with variety of menus and a ambience is so perfect for a family to relax and enjoy.","{'name': ['place', 'hangout', 'people', 'food', 'variety', 'family', 'ambience', 'menus'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,1.9
gerfitzDubai,Decent city hotel,"Limited food choices unless you love curry and rice or spicy food. Rooms are well appointed. Staff were all courteous. Nice pool and outdoor area with bar, although very loud music blaring from the speakers most of the day.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Limited food choices unless you love curry and rice or spicy food. Rooms are well appointed. Staff were all courteous. Nice pool and outdoor area with bar, although very loud music blaring from the speakers most of the day.","{'name': ['food choices', 'food', 'curry', 'rice', 'Rooms', 'area', 'pool', 'speakers', 'music', 'Staff', 'bar'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON', 'OTHER']}",0.3,1.8
Dodger52,Pretty good,"The Kingsbury is located about 20 minutes drive out of Colombo central, At one stage it would have been located on the waterfront but now with significant reclamation going on it is well back from the water with a major construction area in front of it blocking the sea view.It will be good in a view years time when all the work is completed. The hotel is allegedly the only 6 star one in Sri Lanka.  The rooms are large and nice and clean. The WiFi is good and there are plenty of power points with international adapter so no need for a special plug. The shower is excellent with a big shower head and plenty of pressure. The breakfast is wonderful with a huge selection to cater for all.",Date of stay: January 2020,"The Kingsbury is located about 20 minutes drive out of Colombo central, At one stage it would have been located on the waterfront but now with significant reclamation going on it is well back from the water with a major construction area in front of it blocking the sea view.It will be good in a view years time when all the work is completed. The hotel is allegedly the only 6 star one in Sri Lanka.  The rooms are large and nice and clean. The WiFi is good and there are plenty of power points with international adapter so no need for a special plug. The shower is excellent with a big shower head and plenty of pressure. The breakfast is wonderful with a huge selection to cater for all.","{'name': ['stage', 'construction area', 'Kingsbury', 'Colombo', 'reclamation', 'waterfront', 'water', 'work', 'front', 'sea', 'view.It', 'hotel', 'star one', 'shower', 'rooms', 'need', 'plug', 'shower head', 'breakfast', 'plenty', 'all', 'Sri Lanka', 'pressure', 'selection', 'plenty', 'power points', 'adapter', 'WiFi', 'one', 'one', '6', '20'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'ORGANIZATION', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.4,4.5
Milinda G,Great customer service,Madhushika was very helpful and proactive in letting me know the hotel packages on offer. I wish her all the very best in her career. I frequently travel to hotels apart from kingsbury and have not received hospitality upto this standard.so thankyou.,Date of stay: February 2020,Madhushika was very helpful and proactive in letting me know the hotel packages on offer. I wish her all the very best in her career. I frequently travel to hotels apart from kingsbury and have not received hospitality upto this standard.so thankyou.,"{'name': ['Madhushika', 'hotel packages', 'offer', 'best', 'career', 'hospitality', 'kingsbury', 'thankyou', 'hotels'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION']}",0.6,2.0
Lolabugs,"The hotel is beautiful, rooms compact with superior linen and toiletries. Room service provided tasty food.",Our first night after a long and tedious flight from Canada 🇨🇦 was continually disturbed by some unruly guests of a “wedding party “ occupying the adjoining room.  We checked in around 11 am  and noticed a number of noisy men in the hallway. The noise factor continued but got uglier when the unruly highly intoxicated men took the liberty of sprawling in the hallway. One of them knocked at our door around 1:30 am and apologized. The hotel should exercise caution when assigning rooms to ‘one-night only’ patrons who obviously lacked decorum - guess they had they didn’t  care that other guests were trying to rest.  It took me a couple of calls to the front desk and finally the disturbance ceased around 2 am when the people in charges took control. The following nights were without,Date of stay: January 2020,Our first night after a long and tedious flight from Canada 🇨🇦 was continually disturbed by some unruly guests of a “wedding party “ occupying the adjoining room.  We checked in around 11 am  and noticed a number of noisy men in the hallway. The noise factor continued but got uglier when the unruly highly intoxicated men took the liberty of sprawling in the hallway. One of them knocked at our door around 1:30 am and apologized. The hotel should exercise caution when assigning rooms to ‘one-night only’ patrons who obviously lacked decorum - guess they had they didn’t  care that other guests were trying to rest.  It took me a couple of calls to the front desk and finally the disturbance ceased around 2 am when the people in charges took control. The following nights were without,"{'name': ['guests', 'flight', 'Canada 🇨🇦', 'room', 'wedding party', 'noise factor', 'men', 'hallway', 'One', 'hallway', 'men', 'liberty', 'patrons', 'rooms', 'door', 'number', 'hotel', 'caution', 'guests', 'couple', 'desk', 'calls', 'people', 'control', 'disturbance', 'charges', 'decorum', 'nights', '30', 'one', '2', 'One', '1', '11'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'EVENT', 'ORGANIZATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",-0.4,3.4
Rbg,Nice Location,Location is very nice - Hotel was good - great breakfast and dinner buffets - rooms were clean and toiletries good!  Staff was courteous.  Did not visit spa nor the terrace bar - but looked interesting.  Recommend staying there.,Date of stay: January 2020,Location is very nice - Hotel was good - great breakfast and dinner buffets - rooms were clean and toiletries good!  Staff was courteous.  Did not visit spa nor the terrace bar - but looked interesting.  Recommend staying there.,"{'name': ['Location', 'Hotel', 'breakfast', 'dinner buffets', 'toiletries', 'Staff', 'rooms', 'terrace bar', 'spa'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER']}",0.8,3.2
kd_sundarrajan,Best business visit,have been a frequent to this place & i enjoy and appreciate the special attention given to business travelers at 9th Floor lounge with special mention to Mohamed & Shiwangi!...Appreciate your dedication guys!,Date of stay: February 2020,have been a frequent to this place & i enjoy and appreciate the special attention given to business travelers at 9th Floor lounge with special mention to Mohamed & Shiwangi!...Appreciate your dedication guys!,"{'name': ['place', 'attention', 'business travelers', 'lounge', 'Shiwangi', '9th Floor', 'dedication guys', 'mention', 'Mohamed', '9'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,0.9
Prasad V,Birthday Lunch,"On 4th February I took my family to Harbour Court for lunch as it was my elder son's birthday. The food was exceptional in quality and taste. Service was efficient, courteous and professional. Mr. Mark, Buddika, Ranuka and Thilina made this family occasion memorable. Highly recommend.",Date of stay: February 2020,"On 4th February I took my family to Harbour Court for lunch as it was my elder son's birthday. The food was exceptional in quality and taste. Service was efficient, courteous and professional. Mr. Mark, Buddika, Ranuka and Thilina made this family occasion memorable. Highly recommend.","{'name': ['Harbour Court', 'family', 'lunch', 'birthday', 'son', 'food', 'Service', 'quality', 'taste', 'Mark', 'family occasion', 'Ranuka', 'Thilina', 'Buddika', '4th February', '4'], 'type': ['ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'NUMBER']}",0.7,3.9
ududsiri,Excellent food experience on buffet at Harbour Court restautant,Excellent food experience and kind staff at Harbour court restaurant. Specially when checked with some action items on the buffet to prepare some custom food for my kid Mr Jani and Kasun who is waiters paid their attention kindly.,Date of stay: January 2020,Excellent food experience and kind staff at Harbour court restaurant. Specially when checked with some action items on the buffet to prepare some custom food for my kid Mr Jani and Kasun who is waiters paid their attention kindly.,"{'name': ['food experience', 'staff', 'Jani', 'court restaurant', 'Harbour', 'waiters', 'buffet', 'action items', 'food', 'attention', 'Kasun'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,1.8
Isuru Solomons,Birthday of my wife,The food was amazing and unexpectedly the buffet was on fire been a weekday Lunch. Excellent service from the Staff and Kudos to Buddhika and Jason for the extended service.  We were there for almost 2 hours and the hospitality was great. We were almost like home. Thanks guys.,Date of stay: January 2020,The food was amazing and unexpectedly the buffet was on fire been a weekday Lunch. Excellent service from the Staff and Kudos to Buddhika and Jason for the extended service.  We were there for almost 2 hours and the hospitality was great. We were almost like home. Thanks guys.,"{'name': ['food', 'buffet', 'fire', 'Lunch', 'service', 'service', 'Kudos', 'Staff', 'hospitality', 'Jason', 'Buddhika', 'home', 'guys', '2'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,4.5
Gihan De Silva,Good Food,"The hotel has the best High tea in Sri Lanka with lot of varieties. The food quality has improved, since of late. It is a great place to enjoy, relax and rewind. Roof top bar is something else. Keep it up.",Date of stay: January 2020,"The hotel has the best High tea in Sri Lanka with lot of varieties. The food quality has improved, since of late. It is a great place to enjoy, relax and rewind. Roof top bar is something else. Keep it up.","{'name': ['hotel', 'tea', 'place', 'Roof top bar', 'lot', 'varieties', 'Sri Lanka', 'food quality', 'rewind'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.6,3.9
Melanie Derflinger,The best hotel we stayed in while visiting Sri Lanka,We had an absolutely great time in this hotel. The rooms are very spacious and clean and the outdoor pool is really good as well. The hotel has a really nice roof top bar and some really good restaurants with high quality food. The staff was extremely friendly and helpful. Especially the restaurant manager and Kusat and Sarith who really took good care of us. Thank you again!,Date of stay: January 2020,We had an absolutely great time in this hotel. The rooms are very spacious and clean and the outdoor pool is really good as well. The hotel has a really nice roof top bar and some really good restaurants with high quality food. The staff was extremely friendly and helpful. Especially the restaurant manager and Kusat and Sarith who really took good care of us. Thank you again!,"{'name': ['hotel', 'restaurant manager', 'rooms', 'hotel', 'pool', 'restaurants', 'bar', 'food', 'care', 'Kusat', 'Sarith', 'staff'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.9,5.7
Margaret M B,Sunday Lunch,"The manager was very helpful and accommodating. The three piece jazz band was very good. And the food was amazing. The choice, from Sri Lankan to British, was amazing.  Would definitely come back here Great view from the roof of the whole of Colombo",Date of stay: January 2020,"The manager was very helpful and accommodating. The three piece jazz band was very good. And the food was amazing. The choice, from Sri Lankan to British, was amazing.  Would definitely come back here Great view from the roof of the whole of Colombo","{'name': ['manager', 'jazz band', 'food', 'choice', 'view', 'British', 'Sri Lankan', 'roof', 'whole', 'Colombo', 'three'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,4.5
Janet G,Sunday lunch,We came as a group of eight for the Sunday buffet. The choice was amazing and the staff very helpful.  We enjoyed the whole experience. The three piece jazz band added to the ambience too.  Amazing views from the rooftop terrace .,Date of stay: January 2020,We came as a group of eight for the Sunday buffet. The choice was amazing and the staff very helpful.  We enjoyed the whole experience. The three piece jazz band added to the ambience too.  Amazing views from the rooftop terrace .,"{'name': ['group', 'buffet', 'choice', 'staff', 'experience', 'ambience', 'views', 'rooftop terrace', 'jazz band', 'three', 'eight'], 'type': ['ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.6,3.4
Daveweed39,Great buffet,"Great Sunday buffet at the Harbour Court restaurant at the Kingsbury. Wonderful food, excellent jazz band and superb service.The variety of food available was tremendous. I especially enjoyed the selection of Sri Lankan food available. Highly recommended.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Great Sunday buffet at the Harbour Court restaurant at the Kingsbury. Wonderful food, excellent jazz band and superb service.The variety of food available was tremendous. I especially enjoyed the selection of Sri Lankan food available. Highly recommended.","{'name': ['buffet', 'restaurant', 'Harbour Court', 'Kingsbury', 'food', 'food', 'jazz band', 'variety', 'food', 'selection', 'Sri Lankan'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION']}",0.9,3.7
BilalDeCamp,Terrible pool experience,"I checked in today. The hotel itself is good - lovely rooms and setup, nice touches, wonderful checkin etc. but the poolside in the evening has basically ruined everything. We’ve been sitting around waiting to get a menu and drinks. I asked for a menu from someone who did not return. I can see staff milling around not doing much. The music is far too loud for the evening and on the other side of the building is another wedding party, also loud. I can hear the booming noise from the 7th floor room. Why can’t the hotel appreciate that people want a quiet evening and sleep? Absolutely shoddy and it’s left a really sour taste. What a shame. I won’t be staying here again.",Date of stay: January 2020,"I checked in today. The hotel itself is good - lovely rooms and setup, nice touches, wonderful checkin etc. but the poolside in the evening has basically ruined everything. We’ve been sitting around waiting to get a menu and drinks. I asked for a menu from someone who did not return. I can see staff milling around not doing much. The music is far too loud for the evening and on the other side of the building is another wedding party, also loud. I can hear the booming noise from the 7th floor room. Why can’t the hotel appreciate that people want a quiet evening and sleep? Absolutely shoddy and it’s left a really sour taste. What a shame. I won’t be staying here again.","{'name': ['rooms', 'hotel', 'someone', 'touches', 'setup', 'everything', 'checkin', 'menu', 'music', 'menu', 'wedding party', 'staff', 'drinks', 'building', 'side', 'hotel', 'people', 'shame', 'taste', 'floor room', 'noise', '7'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",-0.6,6.8
CvB20152015,"Nice hotel, but terrible overall experience","Nice rooms with sea and sunset views and comfortable in room facilities. The overall staying experience is though comprehensively spoiled by poor overall management, running the place as a 24/7 all round disco. The disco beats from the pool bar echo to dangerous noise levels above the pool for those who wish to swim at sunset. Rooftop bar is unaccessible without ear protection, and its basses resonate over the below hotel floors. Smoking is permitted up to pool edge. The touchscreens of half the fitness equipment are broken, leaving the equipment in state of no use. Management should prioritise being either an entertainment palace for day visitors or offering a city oasis for staying residents.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Nice rooms with sea and sunset views and comfortable in room facilities. The overall staying experience is though comprehensively spoiled by poor overall management, running the place as a 24/7 all round disco. The disco beats from the pool bar echo to dangerous noise levels above the pool for those who wish to swim at sunset. Rooftop bar is unaccessible without ear protection, and its basses resonate over the below hotel floors. Smoking is permitted up to pool edge. The touchscreens of half the fitness equipment are broken, leaving the equipment in state of no use. Management should prioritise being either an entertainment palace for day visitors or offering a city oasis for staying residents.","{'name': ['rooms', 'views', 'sea', 'room facilities', 'Rooftop bar', 'noise levels', 'disco', 'staying experience', 'management', 'equipment', 'place', 'pool', 'disco', 'pool bar echo', 'ear protection', 'hotel floors', 'Management', 'use', 'state', 'basses', 'entertainment palace', 'day visitors', 'residents', 'city oasis', 'fitness equipment', 'Smoking', 'edge', 'touchscreens', '24/7'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",-0.1,4.0
Ashish M,Great Hotel with a splendid view,If you are traveling to Colombo this is one of the best hotels that you can def plan to stay in; great service... amazing options for food and very centrally located.... Great choice of food options available in the hotel; this is great place to spend a couple of days in,Date of stay: January 2020,If you are traveling to Colombo this is one of the best hotels that you can def plan to stay in; great service... amazing options for food and very centrally located.... Great choice of food options available in the hotel; this is great place to spend a couple of days in,"{'name': ['service', 'choice', 'hotels', 'Colombo', 'options', 'food', 'hotel', 'food options', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,2.8
Nadeesha Fernando,Best service ever,"Everything is superb the food was excellent, highly recommended for everyone. Had a memorable dinner at ocean. I like place very much and  peaceful. Friendly and helpful service given by madushika and niroshan  ,sampath. Thank you very much they're make our day.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Everything is superb the food was excellent, highly recommended for everyone. Had a memorable dinner at ocean. I like place very much and  peaceful. Friendly and helpful service given by madushika and niroshan  ,sampath. Thank you very much they're make our day.","{'name': ['Everything', 'food', 'everyone', 'place', 'ocean', 'dinner', 'service', 'niroshan', 'madushika'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.9,4.7
Iran,The best pool bar resturent,This is an amazing pool bar with sunshine I visit. I enjoyed it. Chandana was the person who served us and it was really a good service. Thank you Chandana and thank you Kingsbury. And all the chef's who prepared food for us.,Date of stay: January 2020,This is an amazing pool bar with sunshine I visit. I enjoyed it. Chandana was the person who served us and it was really a good service. Thank you Chandana and thank you Kingsbury. And all the chef's who prepared food for us.,"{'name': ['pool bar', 'Chandana', 'service', 'sunshine', 'chef', 'food', 'Kingsbury'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,4.6
Devi2013,A relaxing vacation at a place that understands great customer service,"Spent three wonderful nights at this hotel. First of all the staff provided great customer service, the breakfasts were sumptuous, the rooms were great - and for those who care, gorgeous soft, too quality Italian Frette linen, robes, towels, and bulgari toiletries.  The location was great - we were able to walk or take tuk tuks to everything. Enjoyed the pool, the roof top club, the gym had well maintained cardio machines and finally, staff accommodated us with a late check out. We will certainly return to this hotel. Thanks to Manjula at the front who took care of us and Kitsiri in the breakfast room for impeccable and thoughtful service. We leave with great memories.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Spent three wonderful nights at this hotel. First of all the staff provided great customer service, the breakfasts were sumptuous, the rooms were great - and for those who care, gorgeous soft, too quality Italian Frette linen, robes, towels, and bulgari toiletries.  The location was great - we were able to walk or take tuk tuks to everything. Enjoyed the pool, the roof top club, the gym had well maintained cardio machines and finally, staff accommodated us with a late check out. We will certainly return to this hotel. Thanks to Manjula at the front who took care of us and Kitsiri in the breakfast room for impeccable and thoughtful service. We leave with great memories.","{'name': ['hotel', 'nights', 'staff', 'customer service', 'rooms', 'tuk tuks', 'location', 'everything', 'gym', 'club', 'robes', 'towels', 'toiletries', 'linen', 'machines', 'pool', 'hotel', 'care', 'breakfasts', 'front', 'Thanks', 'Italian', 'Frette', 'service', 'breakfast room', 'memories', 'Manjula', 'Kitsiri', 'check', 'staff', 'three'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,6.4
SNW,Perfect place for amazing coffee,Lovely ambience and great service. Tried the Saffron Honey latte which was amazing. Interesting concoction which was a welcome surprise. Thanks to Uththara the friendly Barista who made sure everything was just right and Razeen the Manager.,Date of stay: January 2020,Lovely ambience and great service. Tried the Saffron Honey latte which was amazing. Interesting concoction which was a welcome surprise. Thanks to Uththara the friendly Barista who made sure everything was just right and Razeen the Manager.,"{'name': ['ambience', 'service', 'concoction', 'latte', 'Thanks', 'Saffron Honey', 'everything', 'Manager', 'Razeen', 'Barista'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.9,3.7
Anneble,Amazing night,"Food was really Amazing staff service is super super excellent Gautham, Alahakoon,Chandana excellent in overall. Excellent foods and all nice ambience. Overall in a good service. Dinner Buffet is nice .How I chat with them.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Food was really Amazing staff service is super super excellent Gautham, Alahakoon,Chandana excellent in overall. Excellent foods and all nice ambience. Overall in a good service. Dinner Buffet is nice .How I chat with them.","{'name': ['staff service', 'Food', 'Gautham', 'Alahakoon', 'Chandana', 'foods', 'ambience', 'Dinner Buffet', 'service'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER']}",0.8,3.3
sachith i,Great place to Chill,"excellent service the team was very attentive, the food and drinks arrived at the right time manager Nimal, Chandana & Gautham did a great job thanks alot you made our evening...... we enjoied werymuch.....",Date of stay: January 2020,"excellent service the team was very attentive, the food and drinks arrived at the right time manager Nimal, Chandana & Gautham did a great job thanks alot you made our evening...... we enjoied werymuch.....","{'name': ['team', 'service', 'Nimal', 'food', 'drinks', 'Chandana & Gautham', 'job'], 'type': ['ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER']}",0.9,0.9
Rajitha R,Excelent service,"Had a great time in kingsbury hotel honey beach club pool sri lankan bar with friendly staff specially gautham, thilina,manager nimal and Chandana thank you so much and hope to visit  again. Thanks all. Excellent service....",Date of stay: January 2020,"Had a great time in kingsbury hotel honey beach club pool sri lankan bar with friendly staff specially gautham, thilina,manager nimal and Chandana thank you so much and hope to visit  again. Thanks all. Excellent service....","{'name': ['manager nimal', 'hotel honey beach club pool', 'staff', 'thilina', 'bar', 'sri lankan', 'Chandana', 'Thanks', 'all', 'service'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,2.8
Dave Suf smith,Very nice food and nice service,Wow ur good is amazing and service was complite and nice service  thakyou geting that food and new selection and service iforget that waiter thank you very much and again im coming i need to ur fantastic signature cock tailes.❤❤❤😍,Date of stay: January 2020,Wow ur good is amazing and service was complite and nice service  thakyou geting that food and new selection and service iforget that waiter thank you very much and again im coming i need to ur fantastic signature cock tailes.❤❤❤😍,"{'name': ['good', 'food', 'service', 'service', 'waiter', 'service', 'selection', 'iforget', 'thakyou', 'signature cock', '❤❤❤😍'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,0.9
garuka p,New harbour court,Hi  Me and my family had lunch at the harbour court today after the renovations.food is absolutely perfect and so many varieties to select we love seafood and meat both everything was there with different cooking method.overall in colombo I would say best place to have some lunch or dinner and reasonable price as well.  At last I want to mention the waiting staff buddhika and kasun they were very friendly and very polite. They know what they handle.  Thank you again for a lovely lunch   Regards  Garuka punchihewa,Date of stay: January 2020,Hi  Me and my family had lunch at the harbour court today after the renovations.food is absolutely perfect and so many varieties to select we love seafood and meat both everything was there with different cooking method.overall in colombo I would say best place to have some lunch or dinner and reasonable price as well.  At last I want to mention the waiting staff buddhika and kasun they were very friendly and very polite. They know what they handle.  Thank you again for a lovely lunch   Regards  Garuka punchihewa,"{'name': ['lunch', 'family', 'harbour court', 'renovations.food', 'varieties', 'lunch', 'everything', 'seafood', 'cooking', 'colombo', 'place', 'meat', 'dinner', 'price', 'lunch', 'punchihewa', 'waiting staff', 'kasun', 'buddhika', 'Regards Garuka'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,3.7
Tharindu k,One of the best in Colombo,This is one of the best hotels in Colombo! I was there for a function and I must say after the unfortunate Easter Sunday attacks they have rebuilt the place and it was wonderful to see how well they have bounced back! The security levels have increased and the hotel seems eventful! It's an elegant hotel with a wonderful staff as well. The food was nice and the place should be on your list if you are visiting Colombo!,Date of stay: January 2020,This is one of the best hotels in Colombo! I was there for a function and I must say after the unfortunate Easter Sunday attacks they have rebuilt the place and it was wonderful to see how well they have bounced back! The security levels have increased and the hotel seems eventful! It's an elegant hotel with a wonderful staff as well. The food was nice and the place should be on your list if you are visiting Colombo!,"{'name': ['one', 'hotels', 'Colombo', 'function', 'hotel', 'place', 'hotel', 'attacks', 'place', 'security levels', 'food', 'list', 'staff', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,4.7
Kelum K,Overall experience,"Had my parents 50th wedding anniversary which was a huge success, great service ,excellent food. Stayed for 3 nights breakfast buffet was excellent, The service crew was really friendly. Special thanks to, Kasun,Buddhika,Ranuka, at breakfast buffet keep up the good work guys. The Kingsbury Hotel is so lucky to have such dedicated and hardworking staff.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Had my parents 50th wedding anniversary which was a huge success, great service ,excellent food. Stayed for 3 nights breakfast buffet was excellent, The service crew was really friendly. Special thanks to, Kasun,Buddhika,Ranuka, at breakfast buffet keep up the good work guys. The Kingsbury Hotel is so lucky to have such dedicated and hardworking staff.","{'name': ['success', 'parents', 'breakfast buffet', 'service', 'food', 'service crew', 'thanks', 'work guys', 'Buddhika', 'Ranuka', 'Kasun', 'Kingsbury Hotel', 'staff', '3', '50'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,3.8
Nash akme,Best breakfast buffet,My husband and I had a great experience in kingsbury hotel staff was very polite. Breakfast was excellent the gentlemen Buddika & Sanjay who tookcare of our table fast and helpfull & chief jayashingh who makes tasty hoppers (Appa). Next time looking forward to bringing my kids.,Date of stay: January 2020,My husband and I had a great experience in kingsbury hotel staff was very polite. Breakfast was excellent the gentlemen Buddika & Sanjay who tookcare of our table fast and helpfull & chief jayashingh who makes tasty hoppers (Appa). Next time looking forward to bringing my kids.,"{'name': ['husband', 'Buddika & Sanjay', 'experience', 'hotel staff', 'Breakfast', 'gentlemen', 'table', 'jayashingh', 'kids', 'Appa', 'hoppers'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']}",0.9,2.7
Rani S,Sunday brunch at harbour court,Highly recommend to patronise with family.best brunch in Colombo. The spread was very tasty . super variety of food good ambiance and friendly staff and service. Special thanks for Prashanthan  Sushi was amazing! Big variety of desserts too  Definitely we will come soon,Date of stay: January 2020,Highly recommend to patronise with family.best brunch in Colombo. The spread was very tasty . super variety of food good ambiance and friendly staff and service. Special thanks for Prashanthan  Sushi was amazing! Big variety of desserts too  Definitely we will come soon,"{'name': ['brunch', 'Colombo', 'variety', 'spread', 'variety', 'ambiance', 'food', 'service', 'staff', 'desserts', 'thanks', 'Prashanthan Sushi'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,4.7
eurodc,Grand Lady,We stayed in The Kingsbury last weekend for two nights. We also stayed in other five star in Colombo but loved The Kingsbury. This hotel oozes character and we loved it - in fact one of nices hotels I've ever stayed in. Tried the new steakhouse which was great. Had afternon at the pool too which was very nice. Loved staying here and look forward to returning to this Grand old lady with fab staff.,Date of stay: January 2020,We stayed in The Kingsbury last weekend for two nights. We also stayed in other five star in Colombo but loved The Kingsbury. This hotel oozes character and we loved it - in fact one of nices hotels I've ever stayed in. Tried the new steakhouse which was great. Had afternon at the pool too which was very nice. Loved staying here and look forward to returning to this Grand old lady with fab staff.,"{'name': ['The Kingsbury', 'hotel', 'steakhouse', 'character', 'star', 'nices hotels', 'fact', 'Colombo', 'staff', 'lady', 'pool', 'five', 'two', 'one'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.7,4.6
Annie Bucker,Annie Australia,"We stayed at Kingsbury for 2 days in January 2020. Breakfast was good with variety of food. The room of the hotel need to be renovated as it looks a bit old. The swimming pool was good but for a 5 star hotel, it should be compulsory for everyone to have wash before entering the pool. There was a lot of indian people and no one had wash before entering the pool and my husband and I did not go in the pool after seeing that. The top room restaurant is very expensive and we don't recommend anyone to go their. We spent 100 Australian dollars and we were still hungry after that. The Galle face One shopping centre is just 10 minutes walk and there are lots of restaurants downstairs with cheaper food. Overall the service of the hotel was not bad.",Date of stay: January 2020,"We stayed at Kingsbury for 2 days in January 2020. Breakfast was good with variety of food. The room of the hotel need to be renovated as it looks a bit old. The swimming pool was good but for a 5 star hotel, it should be compulsory for everyone to have wash before entering the pool. There was a lot of indian people and no one had wash before entering the pool and my husband and I did not go in the pool after seeing that. The top room restaurant is very expensive and we don't recommend anyone to go their. We spent 100 Australian dollars and we were still hungry after that. The Galle face One shopping centre is just 10 minutes walk and there are lots of restaurants downstairs with cheaper food. Overall the service of the hotel was not bad.","{'name': ['swimming pool', 'Kingsbury', 'food', 'Breakfast', 'room', 'variety', 'hotel', 'pool', 'pool', 'room restaurant', 'star hotel', 'pool', 'wash', 'lot', 'wash', 'no one', 'people', 'everyone', 'husband', 'shopping centre', 'Galle', 'hotel', 'food', 'restaurants', 'service', 'lots', 'anyone', 'Australian', 'January 2020', '100 Australian dollars', '100', '2', '2020', '5', '10', 'one', 'One'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'DATE', 'PRICE', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",-0.2,3.7
Shanika/Nami,Function: 50th Wedding Anniversary,"We just completed celebrating a momentous occasion at Kingsbury Hotel, our parents 50th Wedding Anniversary.   We are so impressed with the hospitality, effort and care at Kingsbury.  From deciding the menu to decorating the hall, the staff helped us, with smile on their faces and a swing in their step.   We would like to especially thank, the staff from Banquets - Harsha for his meticulous planning, Randika for his tireless efforts in ensuring our function ran smoothly and Chamara for all his help!! The staff went over and above.   In addition, the coffee shop Churros became our second home. Uththara took care of our fussy needs and always served us with smile.   We will back soon - Kandegedara Family",Date of stay: January 2020,"We just completed celebrating a momentous occasion at Kingsbury Hotel, our parents 50th Wedding Anniversary.   We are so impressed with the hospitality, effort and care at Kingsbury.  From deciding the menu to decorating the hall, the staff helped us, with smile on their faces and a swing in their step.   We would like to especially thank, the staff from Banquets - Harsha for his meticulous planning, Randika for his tireless efforts in ensuring our function ran smoothly and Chamara for all his help!! The staff went over and above.   In addition, the coffee shop Churros became our second home. Uththara took care of our fussy needs and always served us with smile.   We will back soon - Kandegedara Family","{'name': ['staff', 'occasion', 'parents', 'Kingsbury Hotel', 'Wedding Anniversary', 'staff', 'function', 'care', 'effort', 'hospitality', 'smile', 'efforts', 'step', 'swing', 'Kingsbury', 'faces', 'menu', 'hall', 'Chamara', 'planning', 'care', 'coffee shop', 'home', 'addition', 'smile', 'Banquets - Harsha', 'Randika', 'needs', 'Family', 'Uththara', 'Churros', 'help', '50'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,6.9
Sukesha S,Sky Lounge Bar is the place to be,"Sky Lounge Bar is absolutely hands down the BEST place in the island for cocktails, and a night out. Visit them, it’s worth it. Look out for Chrishan, the super talented young man behind the counter, a mixologist with a zesty spirit, friendly smile and a knack for excellent cocktails. Recommend above everywhere else. Go today!",Date of stay: January 2020,"Sky Lounge Bar is absolutely hands down the BEST place in the island for cocktails, and a night out. Visit them, it’s worth it. Look out for Chrishan, the super talented young man behind the counter, a mixologist with a zesty spirit, friendly smile and a knack for excellent cocktails. Recommend above everywhere else. Go today!","{'name': ['Chrishan', 'Sky Lounge Bar', 'cocktails', 'island', 'place', 'counter', 'cocktails', 'smile', 'knack', 'everywhere', 'spirit'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER']}",0.8,4.1
Dinum sankalpa,"Dinner at Harbour Court, Kingsbury","We had a dinner at the Harbour Court, Kingsbury and the service was extremely good and and all the dishes were amazing and the most delicious ones we've ever had. The food level is Michelin-star level and the Chinese pork, and the salads were amazing and rich in taste. Overall, the dishes were mouth watering and we'd recommend this restaurant to anyone as the dishes are rich in taste, traditions and colour.",Date of stay: January 2020,"We had a dinner at the Harbour Court, Kingsbury and the service was extremely good and and all the dishes were amazing and the most delicious ones we've ever had. The food level is Michelin-star level and the Chinese pork, and the salads were amazing and rich in taste. Overall, the dishes were mouth watering and we'd recommend this restaurant to anyone as the dishes are rich in taste, traditions and colour.","{'name': ['dinner', 'food level', 'Kingsbury', 'Harbour Court', 'service', 'ones', 'dishes', 'salads', 'anyone', 'restaurant', 'Michelin', 'dishes', 'taste', 'Chinese', 'colour', 'traditions', 'pork', 'taste', 'mouth watering', 'dishes'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.9,2.8
Ravi W,Outstanding service and amazing hotel!!,"The Kingsbury is one of the best Hotels along the Galle Face and in all of Sri Lanka. Starting with the Food, the facilities and everything that the hotel has to offer. A special mention must go out to Shameer from the Travel Desk, Chadanda and Dilum from the Honey Beach Club who have given us the most amazing customer service that has never been received by me in the past. The staff are highly trained and deserve a massive round of applause. Thanks for making our stay for our Honeymoon a very memorable one.",Date of stay: January 2020,"The Kingsbury is one of the best Hotels along the Galle Face and in all of Sri Lanka. Starting with the Food, the facilities and everything that the hotel has to offer. A special mention must go out to Shameer from the Travel Desk, Chadanda and Dilum from the Honey Beach Club who have given us the most amazing customer service that has never been received by me in the past. The staff are highly trained and deserve a massive round of applause. Thanks for making our stay for our Honeymoon a very memorable one.","{'name': ['one', 'Hotels', 'Kingsbury', 'Galle Face', 'all', 'everything', 'Sri Lanka', 'facilities', 'Food', 'hotel', 'mention', 'staff', 'applause', 'round', 'Thanks', 'Travel Desk', 'Shameer', 'Dilum', 'Chadanda', 'customer service', 'stay', 'Honeymoon', 'Honey Beach Club', 'one', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'LOCATION', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,4.4
dinusha,Excellent customer service,"I find Ocean restaurant in kingsbury is one if the best seafood restaurants wity delicious food and excellent customer service . Yesterday when i visited with my family to try out seasfood from ocean restaurant, from welcome itself we were well treated by kingsbury ocean restaurant staff.  I really appreciate the amazing attentive customer service of Niroshan,Kusal and sajith and would like to thank them for making our dinner extra special .",Date of stay: January 2020,"I find Ocean restaurant in kingsbury is one if the best seafood restaurants wity delicious food and excellent customer service . Yesterday when i visited with my family to try out seasfood from ocean restaurant, from welcome itself we were well treated by kingsbury ocean restaurant staff.  I really appreciate the amazing attentive customer service of Niroshan,Kusal and sajith and would like to thank them for making our dinner extra special .","{'name': ['restaurant', 'kingsbury', 'Ocean', 'seafood restaurants', 'customer service', 'food', 'seasfood', 'ocean restaurant', 'welcome', 'family', 'ocean restaurant staff', 'sajith', 'dinner', 'Kusal', 'Niroshan', 'customer service', 'one'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,2.5
Riz,Harbour Court Buffett is Best,"Went to have the dinner buffett at Harbour Court earlier this month and found to be the best in Colombo. Been there in previous years but after the recent opening (in Dec 2019), it is more spacious looks classy. The staff (Hiras & Anurudha) were execellent and service was first class. The food; especially the spread and choice is second to none. Had two servings of the roast lamb as it was the best tasted anywhere in Colombo... better that what was served at Cinnamon Grand on New Years Eve. Will definitely go there when in Colombo next... Highly recommeded.",Date of stay: January 2020,"Went to have the dinner buffett at Harbour Court earlier this month and found to be the best in Colombo. Been there in previous years but after the recent opening (in Dec 2019), it is more spacious looks classy. The staff (Hiras & Anurudha) were execellent and service was first class. The food; especially the spread and choice is second to none. Had two servings of the roast lamb as it was the best tasted anywhere in Colombo... better that what was served at Cinnamon Grand on New Years Eve. Will definitely go there when in Colombo next... Highly recommeded.","{'name': ['dinner buffett', 'Colombo', 'Harbour Court', 'service', 'best', 'food', 'Hiras', 'opening', 'spread', 'choice', 'none', 'roast lamb', 'Anurudha', 'Cinnamon Grand', 'servings', 'anywhere', 'Dec 2019', '2019', 'two'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'DATE', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,5.7
Abdul Hafeez,Very good stay,"We stayed here at kingsbury for 3 days..it was wonderfull experience and hospitality given by all staff..specially thanks to vinol,front desk for treating very special and guiding the whole stay....thanks ..will definitely visit again...",Date of stay: January 2020,"We stayed here at kingsbury for 3 days..it was wonderfull experience and hospitality given by all staff..specially thanks to vinol,front desk for treating very special and guiding the whole stay....thanks ..will definitely visit again...","{'name': ['kingsbury', 'thanks', 'experience', 'staff', 'hospitality', 'vinol', 'desk', 'stay', '3'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,0.9
kavindu.h,The best stays,One of the favorite stays for me. Stayed on B&B basis. Excellent spread in the breakfast. Loved the room. The air condition controls were a bit difficult to manage. Staff was very friendly and attentive. Buffet was one of the best in Colombo.,Date of stay: December 2019,One of the favorite stays for me. Stayed on B&B basis. Excellent spread in the breakfast. Loved the room. The air condition controls were a bit difficult to manage. Staff was very friendly and attentive. Buffet was one of the best in Colombo.,"{'name': ['favorite', 'B&B basis', 'room', 'breakfast', 'spread', 'one', 'Buffet', 'best', 'air condition controls', 'Staff', 'Colombo', 'One', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.5,5.2
Thareendra L,Fav Buffet In Colombo,Kingsbury was always one of my fav hotels which has my fav buffet ever since i was a small girl and basically constantly till this very moment.BUT one fine day on Easter Sunday i was right there when everything went out of control in a min! A BOMB BLAST! God knows what went wrong but as an entire nation it was bad fall! since then i wondered how long they would take to be back on there lead! Recently once they reopened i visited the Lunch Buffet and it was mind blowing! hats off for the entire team  for getting back bigger; better and tastier !!! i am just completely in love with it and now its my fav Buffet in Colombo!,Date of stay: January 2020,Kingsbury was always one of my fav hotels which has my fav buffet ever since i was a small girl and basically constantly till this very moment.BUT one fine day on Easter Sunday i was right there when everything went out of control in a min! A BOMB BLAST! God knows what went wrong but as an entire nation it was bad fall! since then i wondered how long they would take to be back on there lead! Recently once they reopened i visited the Lunch Buffet and it was mind blowing! hats off for the entire team  for getting back bigger; better and tastier !!! i am just completely in love with it and now its my fav Buffet in Colombo!,"{'name': ['girl', 'hotels', 'Kingsbury', 'buffet', 'everything', 'control', 'BOMB BLAST', 'nation', 'lead', 'team', 'Buffet', 'love', 'God', 'mind', 'hats', 'Lunch Buffet', 'Colombo', 'one', 'one'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'ORGANIZATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'CONSUMER_GOOD', 'LOCATION', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",0.6,5.2
Dan V,One of the best buffets in Colombo,"Harbour Court was simply amazing. I have been there 3 times since the re-opening and it has been the most amazing food. Tantilizing the taste buds with the variety and amazing service. Always the first choice by our family. Especially yesterday, some of the best service provided by Mr. Prashanthan, the Restuarant Manager. Went all out to make sure that we had whatever we needed, even if it was not on the menu. And the shots of fruit juices that we just pilled up. We ended up finishing the shots, but Mr. Prashanthan still bought out more to make sure we enjoyed. Wonderful service. Amazing experience and the best quality food.  Keep it up Kingsbury!",Date of stay: January 2020,"Harbour Court was simply amazing. I have been there 3 times since the re-opening and it has been the most amazing food. Tantilizing the taste buds with the variety and amazing service. Always the first choice by our family. Especially yesterday, some of the best service provided by Mr. Prashanthan, the Restuarant Manager. Went all out to make sure that we had whatever we needed, even if it was not on the menu. And the shots of fruit juices that we just pilled up. We ended up finishing the shots, but Mr. Prashanthan still bought out more to make sure we enjoyed. Wonderful service. Amazing experience and the best quality food.  Keep it up Kingsbury!","{'name': ['Prashanthan', 'Harbour Court', 're-opening', 'times', 'taste buds', 'variety', 'food', 'service', 'service', 'family', 'choice', 'some', 'menu', 'shots', 'shots', 'service', 'food', 'experience', 'fruit juices', 'Kingsbury', '3'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'ORGANIZATION', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'NUMBER']}",0.8,9.5
Donna G,Harbour court,Once again a top notch meal with excellent service. Will return again and  again. Produce very fresh and expertly cooked. A delight from beginning to end.  Staff very attentive but not at all intrusive. Good management and training.,Date of stay: January 2020,Once again a top notch meal with excellent service. Will return again and  again. Produce very fresh and expertly cooked. A delight from beginning to end.  Staff very attentive but not at all intrusive. Good management and training.,"{'name': ['notch meal', 'service', 'delight', 'management', 'training', 'Staff'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON']}",0.9,5.6
Sasi R,Great Service!,The service here is brilliant! I recommend trying the Sunday buffet - guaranteed too many choices to try in one sitting.  Waiter Jani deserves special mention for going out of his way to make sure we had everything we needed.,Date of stay: January 2020,The service here is brilliant! I recommend trying the Sunday buffet - guaranteed too many choices to try in one sitting.  Waiter Jani deserves special mention for going out of his way to make sure we had everything we needed.,"{'name': ['service', 'Waiter Jani', 'choices', 'sitting', 'way', 'everything', 'mention', 'one'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'NUMBER']}",0.9,2.7
Ian Gilmour,Restaurant Review,Sunday lunch is exceptional. Jani served us and Dhanushka looked after our booking. The range of food is terrific. Will return soon as have been before and the service matches the food. We recommend the bubbly with the buffet.,Date of stay: January 2020,Sunday lunch is exceptional. Jani served us and Dhanushka looked after our booking. The range of food is terrific. Will return soon as have been before and the service matches the food. We recommend the bubbly with the buffet.,"{'name': ['lunch', 'Jani', 'range', 'food', 'booking', 'Dhanushka', 'food', 'buffet', 'bubbly', 'service'], 'type': ['EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.6,3.1
Mevan,Best fine dining experience in Colombo.,Kingsbury Hotel’s Harbour Court Resturent is the best buffet in Colombo.   # Great food # More varieties # Nice atmosphere # Great service  Best place to have meal with family and friends.   Nice fine dining experience.  Keep up the good service. Good Luck.   Thanks.,Date of stay: January 2020,Kingsbury Hotel’s Harbour Court Resturent is the best buffet in Colombo.   # Great food # More varieties # Nice atmosphere # Great service  Best place to have meal with family and friends.   Nice fine dining experience.  Keep up the good service. Good Luck.   Thanks.,"{'name': ['Harbour Court Resturent', 'Kingsbury Hotel', 'buffet', 'Colombo', 'service', 'atmosphere', 'food', 'varieties', 'place', 'family', 'meal', 'service', 'Thanks', 'Good Luck', 'friends', 'dining experience'], 'type': ['LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER']}",0.7,4.7
Paul Carr,Service Has Dropped,"We are regular visitors here and as such that implies we must like the place, and we do. Since the bomb blast last April naturally a few alterations have been made as well as a few that were planned anyway.   Having booked directly with the hotel months back our intial observations were disappointing as I had booked 2 rooms, one for my wife and I and one for my brother and his wife, yet were charged two different rates by 2 different payment methods. I think when my brother paid they simply converted the $ rate to £ yet for mine for some reason they converted it to Sri Lankan Rupees and then to Pounds resulting in me paying £40 more for the same thing. This is just wrong and needs a consistent approach.  We also didn't get the Galle Face road view rooms we had booked instead",Date of stay: January 2020,"We are regular visitors here and as such that implies we must like the place, and we do. Since the bomb blast last April naturally a few alterations have been made as well as a few that were planned anyway.   Having booked directly with the hotel months back our intial observations were disappointing as I had booked 2 rooms, one for my wife and I and one for my brother and his wife, yet were charged two different rates by 2 different payment methods. I think when my brother paid they simply converted the $ rate to £ yet for mine for some reason they converted it to Sri Lankan Rupees and then to Pounds resulting in me paying £40 more for the same thing. This is just wrong and needs a consistent approach.  We also didn't get the Galle Face road view rooms we had booked instead","{'name': ['visitors', 'place', 'brother', 'few', 'alterations', 'bomb blast', 'wife', 'wife', 'one', 'rates', 'rooms', 'hotel', 'payment methods', 'road view rooms', 'more', 'Pounds', 'thing', 'observations', 'approach', 'rate', 'mine', 'reason', 'Galle Face', 'Sri Lankan Rupees', '£40', 'one', '40', 'two', '2', 'one', '2'], 'type': ['PERSON', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'EVENT', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'ORGANIZATION', 'PRICE', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER', 'NUMBER']}",-0.4,4.0
Sera,Dinner,Enjoyed really well at the harbour court buffet Pleasant n really tasty food I guess the largest buffet in colombo Specially need to thank buddika about Professional service given to us. Enjoyed the night♥️,Date of stay: January 2020,Enjoyed really well at the harbour court buffet Pleasant n really tasty food I guess the largest buffet in colombo Specially need to thank buddika about Professional service given to us. Enjoyed the night♥️,"{'name': ['Pleasant n', 'harbour court buffet', 'buffet', 'buddika', 'service'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'PERSON', 'OTHER']}",0.9,1.9
Inspiration438726,Dinner buffet,Very good friendly atmosphere Delicious foods.excellent service. We have been visited this hotel from many years. Well recommended. Hotel staff very friendly and kind service with costumers. We can enjoy with many variety of tasty foods.,Date of stay: January 2020,Very good friendly atmosphere Delicious foods.excellent service. We have been visited this hotel from many years. Well recommended. Hotel staff very friendly and kind service with costumers. We can enjoy with many variety of tasty foods.,"{'name': ['atmosphere', 'service', 'hotel', 'Hotel staff', 'foods', 'variety', 'service', 'costumers'], 'type': ['OTHER', 'OTHER', 'LOCATION', 'PERSON', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER', 'OTHER']}",0.7,3.8
